Joseph Niifio Tetteh

Tel: 044 540 238 josephniifio@gmail.com https://josephniifio-portfolio.netlify.app/

Add: Davitashen, Yerevan, Armenia.

Profile

Innovative and task-driven professional with three years plus of experience in web design and development. Prepared to work with an encouraging and stable company that will assist me with developing, improving and obtaining the necessary skills to enhance my skills and be efficient.

Experience

Web Developer, Freelance, Yerevan.

May 2021 - Present.

-Build and edit website for clients.

Web Developer, SACNIP Consult, Accra, Ghana.

January 2020 - May 2021

-Team member, help to build, maintain and regularly update company's websites and blogs.

ESL Teacher, Gaby's English Training School, Chengdu, China.

October 2011 - Nov 2019

-Lead ESL Teacher, train new and junior ESL teachers.

Mathematics Teacher, Ghana International College.

March 2010 - September 2011

– Mathematics teacher, help students understand and develop basic technics in mathematics.

Education

Specialized programing courses (Codecademy, Udemy, FreeCodeCamp).

2019 - Present.

MSc. Finance, Southwestern University of Finance and Economics, Chengdu China.

June | 2018

BSc. Mathematics with Economics, University of Development Studies, Navrongo, Ghana.

September | 2009

Skills

Software languages, frameworks and libraries worked with include:

Javascript	• HTML	Material UI
• Node Js	• Flutter	• Ant Design
• React Js	Sanity	• Chakra UI
• Next Js	• Tailwind	• MongoDB
• CSS	Bootstrap	

Projects

Projects completed include:

- https://josephniifio-portfolio.netlify.app/
- https://hombuddy-realestate-7hc1os7zs-josephniifio-gmailcom.vercel.app
- https://cryptobase-niifio.netlify.app/

- https://restaurant-niifio.netlify.app/
- https://flex-pics.netlify.app

Languages spoken:

--- English -- Chinese - French